http://www.parsimonious.org/support/web-privacy-policy.html

Extra Information: Furniture
Where Can I Find..?
How Do I Make Custom Content?
Extra Information: Houses
Where Can I Find..?
How Do I Make Custom Content?
Extra Information: Worlds
How Do I Make Custom Content?
Parsimonious Privacy Policy
Parsimonious may collect, store and use the following kinds of data:-
Your IP address, browser type, referral source, length & frequency of visits and number of page views whilst browsing the site
Your email address is recorded if you provide me with it by emailing me or the website support address
Please note the above is standard data that ALL websites collect. Email addresses for enquiries are not kept on our web servers.
About Cookies
Due to the introduction of European Union legislation on privacy we now use cookies for the sole purpose of telling your browser whether or not you've seen the notice we must carry about cookies when you visit us. This law says that we have to have this notice and it's associated cookie because although our website doesn't use cookies for any other purpose, the advertising networks who provide our adverts do and it's our job to make sure our visitors know this.
For More Information:
What Are Cookies: Cookies Explained
Policies & Principals - Google Adsense
Privacy Policy - Index Exchange
* Any cookies set by our site prior to this time will have expired by now.
How Parsimonious uses your data
Kate says: If you email the support service with a message requiring a response, I will only use that email address to attempt to contact you on matters relating to the issue you raised. The contents of your message may be shared with other Parsimonious staff members if the query relates to their creations and requires them to contribute towards the answer BUT all staff members are also legally bound to honor the site's privacy policy.
We will NOT share personal data with ANY 3rd party except in very exceptional circumstances where it is necessary to report details of serious illegal activity.
Please note that there will always be the possibility of an unauthorized breach of the site's web servers, it is sadly the nature of the internet. Under such circumstances I have no control over how stored data may be used and am not responsible for the consequences, however, I have taken every reasonable precaution to prevent this.
Have a question? Ask Kate!
Copyright Parsimonious 2003 - 2020 ~ All rights reserved ~ View Parsimonious Privacy Policy here
This site is not affiliated with Electronic Arts or any of it's partners or any other games publishers or any other makers of anything...
